A Guide to the Lanier Garden Club Records 1954-1989
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
Special Collections, James Madison University
Lanier Garden Club Records 1954-1989
Special Collections, James Madison University
2080
This collection consists of 3 flat boxes.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Deposited by the Harrisonburg-Rockingham Historical Society in September, 1989.
Biographical/Historical Information
The Lanier Garden Club, named after the poet Sidney Lanier, was organized in Harrisonburg in 1954.
Scope and Content
This collections contains ten scrapbooks of clippings, photos, and programs, and one yearbook.
Arrangement
Flat Box 1: Scrapbooks 1955-1960, Flat Box 2: Scrapbooks 1960-1964, Flat Box 3: Scrapbooks 1964-1966 and Yearbooks 1987-1989.
Contents List
- Flat Box 1
  - Scrapbook 1955-1956
  - Scrapbook 1956-1957
  - Scrapbook 1958-1959
  - Scrapbook 1959-1960
- Flat Box 2
  - Scrapbook 1960-1961
  - Scrapbook 1961-1962
  - Scrapbook 1962-1963
  - Scrapbook 1963-1964
- Flat Box 3
  - Scrapbook 1964-1965
  - Scrapbook 1965-1966
  - Yearbook 1987-1988-1989